https://www.thevehiclelab.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy Effective date: June 11, 2020 The Vehicle Lab ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://www.thevehiclelab.com/ website (hereinafter referred to as the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our site and the choices you have associated with that data. We use your data to provide and improve the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, the terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible below. Definitions Site - Site is the https://www.thevehiclelab.com/ website operated by The Vehicle LabPersonal Data - Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).Usage Data - Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Site or from the Site's infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).Cookies - Cookies are small files stored on your device (computer or mobile device).Data Controller - Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.Data Processors (or Service Providers) - Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.Data Subject (or User) - Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data. Information Collection and Use We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Site to you. Types of Data Collected Personal Data We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website (contact forms and comments section). Usage Data We may collect information on how the Website is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic and analytical data. Tracking & Cookies Data We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Site and we hold certain information. Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Other tracking technologies are also used such as beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Site. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Website. These are some of the most common browsers and ways to disable cookies on them: Google Chrome Mozilla Firefox Internet Explorer Safari If you don't see your browser listed, you can search for it online and find the appropriate help documents provided by the company who supports your browser. Examples of Cookies we use: Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Site.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Advertising Cookies. Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests. Use of Data The Vehicle Lab uses the collected data for various purposes: To provide and maintain our SiteTo provide customer supportTo gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our SiteTo monitor the usage of our SiteTo detect, prevent and address technical issues Analytics We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Site. Clicky - Clicky is a web analytics service. Read the Privacy Policy for Clicky here: https://clicky.com/terms Advertising We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Site. Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie - Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Site or other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/You may also opt out of Google Analytics any time via this link. Amazon Affiliate Disclosure We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates.
Learn more about our affiliate disclosure here: Amazon Affiliate Disclosure Links to Other Sites Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. Children's Privacy Our Site does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. Changes to This Privacy Policy We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the updated date on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. Contact Us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: By visiting this page on our website: https://www.thevehiclelab.com/contact/ Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use Terms By accessing this website, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws, and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law. Use License Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on thevehicelab.com’s web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license, you may not: Modify or copy the materials;Use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);Attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on thevehiclelab.com’s web site; remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; orTransfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server. Disclaimer The materials on thevehiclelab.com's web site are provided “as is”. Thevehiclelab.com makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, thevehiclelab.com does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site. Limitations In no event shall thevehiclelab.com be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on thevehiclelab.com’s Internet site, even if thevehiclelab.com or a thevehiclelab.com authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you. Revisions and Errata The materials appearing on thevehiclelab.com’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Thevehiclelab.com does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Thevehiclelab.com may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Thevehiclelab.com does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials. Links Thevehiclelab.com has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by thevehiclelabcom of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk. Site Terms of Use Modifications Thevehiclelab.com may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use. Governing Law Any claim relating to thevehiclelab.com’s web site shall be governed by the laws without regard to its conflict of law provisions. Copyright © 2020AboutContactAmazon Affiliate DisclosurePrivacy PolicySitemapThevehiclelab.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for website owners to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon(.com, .co.uk, .ca etc) and any other website that may be affiliated with Amazon Service LLC Associates Program.
linkedin
facebook
pinterest
youtube
rss
twitter
instagram
facebook-blank
